[
	{
		"question": "Who is the property of being authentic and being able to be verified and trusted?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9797407984733582,
			"start": 950,
			"end": 962,
			"answer": "Authenticity"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is an attempt to alter system resources or affect their operation?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9530361890792847,
			"start": 0,
			"end": 13,
			"answer": "Active attack"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is a particular focus in this category?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.9463707804679871,
			"start": 1335,
			"end": 1354,
			"answer": "Web server software"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of the term that covers two related concepts?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.8743918538093567,
			"start": 1342,
			"end": 1356,
			"answer": "Accountability"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the origin of the attack?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.821284830570221,
			"start": 261,
			"end": 274,
			"answer": "Inside attack"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "Who knows everything about the infrastructure of the organisation and will know when to the possible human attack surface",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.7425997257232666,
			"start": 666,
			"end": 679,
			"answer": "the adversary"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What does a system perform in an unimpaired manner?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.6393283009529114,
			"start": 826,
			"end": 847,
			"answer": "its intended function"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "Who is the insider authorized to access system resources?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.5360894203186035,
			"start": 289,
			"end": 328,
			"answer": "an entity inside the security perimeter"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of a card-reader website server?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.40306150913238525,
			"start": 111,
			"end": 135,
			"answer": "1.4: Low confidentiality"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is a good tradeoff for Defamation, private information, High confidentiality?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.2882665693759918,
			"start": 456,
			"end": 493,
			"answer": "extremely sensitive data Low-moderate"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What does logical access control provide for protecting cryptographic software from tampering and the keys from replacement or disclosure?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.2519945800304413,
			"start": 59,
			"end": 127,
			"answer": "isolating cryptographic software from other parts of the host system"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the name of the person who is responsible for generating questions?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.1657295525074005,
			"start": 0,
			"end": 1,
			"answer": "."
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "How many outside attackers are in the Internet?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.13106130063533783,
			"start": 653,
			"end": 745,
			"answer": "amateur pranksters to organized criminals, international terrorists, and hostile governments"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What is an access card to ensure confidentiality and a password that goes with it?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.09916803985834122,
			"start": 1518,
			"end": 1545,
			"answer": "Group theory Exercises: 1.1"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "What does the term \"data confidentiality\" mean?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 0.03678695112466812,
			"start": 1358,
			"end": 1375,
			"answer": "The security goal"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 1.2563124073494691e-5,
			"start": 1672,
			"end": 1737,
			"answer": "we must be able to trace a security breach to a responsible party"
		}
	},
	{
		"question": "?",
		"answer": {
			"score": 7.842867489671335e-6,
			"start": 13,
			"end": 91,
			"answer": "logical access control may provide a means of isolating cryptographic software"
		}
	}
]
